Guide to the American Federation of Teachers, Local 2067 Records, 1966-1980 AIS.1981.15
ULS Archives & Special Collections
American Federation of Teachers, Local 2067 Records
1966-1980
ULS Archives & Special Collections
American Federation of Teachers. Local 2067 (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
AIS.1981.15
6.25 Linear Feet (5 boxes)
American Federation of Teachers Local 2067 represents full-time and part-time faculty at the Community College of Allegheny County in Pittsburgh, Pa. This collection contains information regarding Local 2067 and its interactions with CCAC.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Harry E. Leas in 1981.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Arrangement
Series I. General Files
Series II. American Federation of Teachers
Series III. Contract Research
Series IV. American Federation of Teachers, Local 2067
Series V. College Relations
History
American Federation of Teachers, Local 2067 represents full-time and part-time faculty at the Community College of Allegheny County in Pittsburgh, Pa. The local was certified in 1971 as the bargaining agent for professors and technicians at CCAC. In addition to determining details on curriculum and salary rates, the union also provided input regarding administrative matters and searches for new school presidents.
Previous Citation
American Federation of Teachers, Local 2067 Records, 1966-1980, AIS.1981.15, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
This collection contains information regarding Local 2067 and its interactions with the Community College of Allegheny County. Included are records about contract negotiations, as well as research about other faculty unions throughout the country.
Related Material
American Federation of Teachers Local 2340 Records, 1971-1983, AIS.1983.23, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
American Federation of Teachers Local 2097 Records, 1970-1982, AIS.1983.03, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Labor; Education; College teachers' unions -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh.; American Federation of Teachers. Local 2067 (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Community College of Allegheny County; American Federation of Teachers
- General Files, I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series contains research regarding teachers and education. Also included are documents about several conferences and groups concerned with educators and labor unions.
  - Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining: Evaluations Material, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Conference of Academic Unionists, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - AAUP-Temple Contract, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - State Master Plan, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6-8)
  - Act 195 Study Commission, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - CUNY-Legislative Conference Contract, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - PSEA Community College Locals, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AAUP Academic Freedom Guidelines and Budget Lobby, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Commission for Community Colleges, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Pennsylvania Post Secondary Planning Commission, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - AAUP Governance Statement, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Agency Shop Information, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Pennsylvania Community College Regulations, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
  - Union Information, Pittsburgh Area Colleges, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Decertification Efforts, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Act 195 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - State College Bargaining Rights Case, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Department of Education, Statistical Publications, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Higher Education with Fewer Teachers, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Professional Association Minutes, 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 25-26)
  - Professional Association, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 27-38)
- American Federation of Teachers, II.
  This series contains information about the American Federation of Teachers and their locals in Pennsylvania. Included are records from the AFT council in southwestern Pennsylvania, as well as locals in the Philadelphia area. Also present is information regarding the Pennsylvania Federation of Teachers.
  - Association of Pennsylvania State College and University Faculty, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - AFT Southwestern Pennsylvania Area Council, Minutes and Agendas, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - AFT Southwestern Pennsylvania Area Council Local's Newsletters, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - AFT Southwestern Pennsylvania Area Council, State Retirement, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - AFT Southwestern Pennsylvania Area Council (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Pennsylvania Locals, IRS, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Local 2026 (FFCCP) Newsletter, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 45-47)
  - Local 2026 (FFCCP) Constitution, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Local 2026 (FFCCP) Contract, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Local 2026 (FFCCP) Salary Survey, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Local 2026 (FFCCP) Part Time Faculty, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Union Teacher Press Association, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Local 3 (Philadelphia) Reporter, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Local 3 (Philadelphia), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Central Labor Council, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Pennsylvania Federation of Teachers Convention, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 56-59)
  - Pennsylvania Federation of Teachers, Colleges VP Mailings, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 60-62)
  - Pennsylvania Federation of Teachers Certification, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Pennsylvania Federation of Teachers Special Education, Federal Law, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 64-65)
  - Pennsylvania Federation of Teachers Special Education Publication, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Pennsylvania Federation of Teachers VP Testimony, State Board of Education, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Pennsylvania Federation of Teachers, President Richman Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Pennsylvania Federation of Teachers, Pennsylvania Teacher, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - American Federation of Teachers Convention, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 70-73)
  - American Federation of Teachers Accident/Disability Insurance Benefits (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - American Federation of Teachers Life Insurance Benefits (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - American Federation of Teachers Dental Insurance Benefits (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - American Federation of Teachers Professional Liability Insurance Benefits (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - American Federation of Teachers Union Liability Insurance Benefits (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - American Federation of Teachers Retirees Life Insurance Benefits (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - American Federation of Teachers Benefits (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - American Federation of Teachers, Sample Contract (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Milwaukee Technical College Local 212 Contract, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Teachers Pamphlets, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - American Federation of Teachers Sample Contract (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - American Federation of Teachers on Campus, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - American Federation of Teachers Position Papers, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - American Federation of Teachers, Excerpts from Ececutive Council Minutes, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - American Federation of Teachers African Drought Project, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - American Federation of Teachers Financial Aid Questionaires (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Federation of Teachers Quest Information, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - American Federation of Teachers Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - American Federation of Teachers, AFT Action, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - George Meany Labor Center (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Contract Research, III.
  This series includes research regarding contracts between universities and colleges and faculty unions. Parts of or entire union contracts with colleges are present, as well as files on each issue addressed in Local 2067's own contract with CCAC.
  - Displacement (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Renewals and Tenure (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Rights and Privilages of the Federation (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Compensation and Fringe Benefits (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Letter of Understanding (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Practices and Policies, Bucks Coutny Community College (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Definitions (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - College Schedule (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Credit for Previous Experiences (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Macomb County Community College, Michigan, 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 24-25)
  - Madison Technical College Teachers, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Metropolitan Community College, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Middlesex County College, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Milwaukee Area Vocational and Technical, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Minnesota State College, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Nassau Community College, 1969-1975 (Box 2, Folder 31-33)
  - Niagra County Community College, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Oakland (Michigan) Community College, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Parkway West Federation of Teachers, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Pennsylvania State College Faculty, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
  - Philadelphia Community College, 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Pittsburgh Federation of Teachers, 1971-1978 (Box 2, Folder 41-43)
  - Rhode Island College, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - University of Rhode Island, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Rockland Community College, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Somerset County College Federation, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Southwestern Oregon Community College, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 48-49)
  - Temple Univeristy, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Dade County Public Schools, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Deleware County Community College, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - El Camino Community College, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Green River Community College, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Henry Ford Community College, 1968-1973 (Box 2, Folder 55-56)
  - Illinois State Colleges, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Indian River Community College, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 58-59)
  - Jackson Community College, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Lehigh County Community College, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Los Angeles Community College, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Beaver County Community College, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Belleville Area College, 1970-1971, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 64-65)
  - Boston State College, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Bucks County Community College, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 67-68)
  - Camden County College, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Chicago City College, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Clairton Education Association, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - City College of New York (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Contra Costa Community College, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Cook County Community College Teachers, 1969, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 74-75)
  - Contracts (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Allegheny County Community College (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Alaska Community College, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Allegheny Campus Time Schedules (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Association of Pennsylvania State College and University Faculty, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Baltimore Community College, 1975-1976, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 81-82)
  - Bay de Noc Community College, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Washtenaw County Community College, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Wayne State University, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - West Mifflin, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Westchester County, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Westmoreland Community College, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - West Virginia University (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Whatcom Community College, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Changes in Institutional Organization (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Additional Facilities (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Instructional Technology (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Academic Calendar (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Department Responsibilities to Part Time Employees (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Headings (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Totality of Agreements (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Separability (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Term of Agreement (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Tuition Reimbursement (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - General Provisions (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Advisement (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Advertising and Transfer (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Right to Return to Unit (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Personnel File (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Academic Freedom (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Federation Security (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Fair Practices (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Recognition (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Responsibilities of the Parties (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Strikes and Lock Outs (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Grievance Proceedures (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Management Rights (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Promotions (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Salary Schedule (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Employment Arrangements (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Vacations (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Department Head (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Campus Committees (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Leaves of Absence (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Evaluation Procedures (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Evaluation (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Disciplines or Areas (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Working Conditions (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Seniority (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Holidays (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Termination of Employment (Box 3, Folder 45)
- American Federation of Teachers, Local 2067 at the Community College of Allegheny County, IV.
  This series includes records concerning the activities of Local 2067. Included are newsletters and member lists. Election materials and mailings are also present.
  - Federation Forum, 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Weekly Bulletin, 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Constitution, 1970-1980 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Cancer Care Insurance, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Quest Conference (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Officer Elections, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 52-53)
  - Negotiating Committee Newsbrief, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Faculty Tri-Campus Newsletter, June-September 1974 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Faculty In-Campus Newsletter, October 1974 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Mailing List, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Part Time Faculty Articles (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Part Time Faculty Questionaires, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 60-65)
  - Faculty Age, Sex, Race and Salary (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Arbitration Cases, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Membership Meeting Notices and Agendas, 1972-1980 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Presidential Mailings to Members, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Mailing List, Birthdays, Membership List, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Organization Drive (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Campus Vice-President Mailings, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - County Commissioner Election Endorsement, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Committee Elections, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Contract, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- College Relations, V.
  This series contains information about CCAC. Included are questionaires, reports, and minutes that provide samples of the concerns teachers, students, and administration were addressing during the 1970s.
  - Physics Department, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 79-83)
  - Nursing Department, Chairperson Grievance, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Nursing Department, Proposed By-Laws, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Nursing Department, Local 2067 Nursing Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Nursing Department, Articulated Program, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Nursing Department, Articulated Program, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 2-8)
  - Nursing Department, Negotiations, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 9-10)
  - Allied Health, New Course Proposal, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Allied Health, New Curriculum Proposal, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
  - Allied Health, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Psychology Department, Department Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Psychology Department, Course Load, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Psychology Department, Human Behavior Course (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Psychology Department, Text Book Selection, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Psychology Department, Course Scheduling and Seniority, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Pedology Program, Prison Program Cutbacks, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Pedology Program, Graduate Survey (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Pedology Program, Course Cancellation, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - VUE, Freedom of the Press, 1972, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 23-26)
  - Student Affairs Committee Minutes, 1969-1978 (Box 4, Folder 27-30)
  - Operations Manual for Student Activities, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Student Association Constitution, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Student Events Conduct Guidelines, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Student Affairs Committee Memos, 1969-1978 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Middle States Evaluation, 1969-1978 (Box 4, Folder 35-54)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1968, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 55-61)
  - Board of Trustees Personnel Policies, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Board of Trustees, Presidential Search, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 63-64)
  - Board of Trustees, Braden Petition, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Calendar, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Course Scheduling, 1974-1979 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Catalog, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Engineering Workland Survey, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Class Size, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - CMU Teacher Training, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Newsletter, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Continuing Education Questionaire, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Student Markets, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 74-75)
  - Instructional Materials Production Center, Annual Report, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Instructional Materials Production Center Reorganization, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Time Cards, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Supervisory Classroom Observation Forms (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Student Outcomes Questionaires, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Day-Evening Articulation Committee, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Ad-Hoc Committee on Clerical Services, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - 25% Differential Arbitration, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - HEMI Survey Results, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - General Administrative Staff Meeting Minutes, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - HEMI Background Information, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Grading, "I" and "W", 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Educational Professions Development Act Conference, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Energy Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Continuing Education, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Job Announcements, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Day Care Centers, 1973-1978 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Career and Transfer Committee, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Summer School Problems, 1973-1978 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Student Withdrawl Survey, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Workload Grievance, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Building Complaints, West Hall, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Building Complaints, Allegheny Campus, 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Administration Sponsored Workshops, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Admissions/Academic Standards Committee, 1972-1979 (Box 5, Folder 6-11)
  - Academic Policy Committee Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 12-14)
  - Academic Policy Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Affirmative Action, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 16-18)
  - Bargaining Unit Classifications, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Development Education Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Clerical Workers Election, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 21-23)
  - Copyright Law Workshops, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Manpower Training, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Library, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Learning Experience Assessment Program, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - South Campus Reorganization, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Public Relations, 1974-1979 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Dean of Instruction Memos, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Orientation Committee, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - PPBS Program (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Peer Counceling, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - PHEAA Course Reduction, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - PHEAA Regulations, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Master Plan, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Intercampus Academic Council, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Ad-Hoc Committee on Reorganization, 1972-1977 (Box 5, Folder 38-39)
  - Academic and Educational Services Division Minutes, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Committee on Reorganization of Educational Services, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Super Ad-Hoc Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Evaluation of Administration, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Wage Freeze, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Faculty Evaluations, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Lynn Adams Grievance, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Admissions Survey, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - CCAC Budget, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Nancy Kuhn Collegial Coverage Grievance, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 50-51)
  - Local 2067 Administrative Costs and Accountability Report, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Operating Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 53-54)
  - Administrator and Trustees List, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Carley/Hughes Work Load Grievance, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Allegheny Campus Planning Committee, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Committee on Clerical Services, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Promotion Cases, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Scheduling and Work Load Grievance, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Academic Calendar Committee, 1974-1979 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Instructional TV, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Staffing Report, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Campus AAUP Chapter, 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 64-65)
  - Negotiations, 1971-1980 (Box 5, Folder 66-68)
  - Make Up Lunch Time, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Behavioral Sciences Workload Grievance, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Engineering Workload, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - AFT/SEIU/CCAS Employee Assistance Program (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Dean Evanko Meetings, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Calendar Committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Curriculum Committee Vacancy, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - "Hold" Classes", 1978 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Math Department Grievances, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Administrative Evaluation Committee, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973-1980 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Building the Grounds, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Education Technicians Attendance Reports, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Meet and Discuss, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Bargaining Unit Challenge, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - President Mack Speech to Trustees, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Forms, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Negotiation Minutes, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - CCAC Federation of Teachers, Local 2067 Constitution (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Status of Negotiations, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Paraprofessional Salary Schedule, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Employment Data, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Negotiations, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Incomplete Contract Proposal, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Incomplete Contract, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 93-94)